glory of Russia brother Good afternoon And what is
слава России брат Добрый день А в чем
Russia's words I always wonder when
Россия слова Мне интересно всегда когда
what is the glory of Russia Tell normally there is
в чем слава России Расскажите нормально
nothing to explain why the words of Russia I
нечего объяснить почему слова России
love this moment
люблю этот момент
Tell me what the glory of Russia is
Расскажи в чем слава России
the greatest powerful state
самая великая могущественная держава
[ __ ]
[__]
further than the glory of Russia you
дальше чем слава России ты пальцы
bend your fingers I am Great power America
загибай я Великая держава Америка
Great  power Yes, technological
Великая держава Да технологическая
pre-war everything super
довоенная все супер
bang can take a year Come on further than the
бахнуть может год взять Давай дальше чем
glory of Russia
слава России
Look what other country can be in the 21st
Смотри какая еще страна может быть в 21
century
веке
to get territory
получить территории
in what Great Let's think think
в чем Великая Давай думай думай
What else can a country in the 21st century
Какая еще может страна 21 веке
neighbors something Temporarily yes
соседей что-то Временно да
After a while it will be forever
Спустя время будет навсегда
So in  what is the great country
Так в чем вот в чем великая страна
Russia Damn, here are two fingers back too
Россия Блин вот два пальца тоже назад
Damn, I still have enough fingers, come on,
Блин у меня еще пальцев хватает давай
as long as there are enough fingers Come on, what is the glory of
пока пальцев хватает Давай в чем слава
Russia and where are you now in
России а ты где сейчас находишься в
Russia You don’t run away you started the words
России Ты не убегает ты начал слова
Russia
России
loves the moment when
обожает момент когда
two funny ones
два смешных
are so for everyone
так по всем
tell me come on I'm serious I'll
расскажи Давай я серьезно я буду тебя
track you like a teacher on an exam tell
трек как учитель на экзамене Расскажите
a student at h  I eat the glory of Russia some kind of
студент в чем слава России какой-то
student Here I am as if your
студент Вот я как будто бы твой
teacher You have to name 5 words of
преподаватель Ты должен назвать 5 слов
Russia 2 you are there well Hey In short, I’m like a
России 2 ты там ну Хей Короче я как
normal teacher, I’ll count there so that they
нормальный препод я там зачту чтобы
don’t kick you out dishonestly Come on
вообще не выгнали тебя нечестно Давай
five more
еще пять
Well, firstly, third, more precisely, this
Ну во-первых третьих точнее уже это
many national side the most
много национальная сторона самая
multinational country
многонациональная страна
in which Glory lives a lot of people and that
в чем Слава живут куча народу и что
in China there is a huge number of
в Китае огромное количество
nationalities in India there are
национальностей в Индии количество
many nationalities And that we have the most Well,
национальностей много И что так у нас
let's say that there is a lot a
больше всех Ну допустим что там куча
lot in which Glory does not fit
куча в чем Слава не подходит
Maybe
Может
you live better than anyone, for example,
вы живете лучше всех например
now the territory  it will become even more
сейчас территория еще больше станет
it doesn’t combine on the fingers Yes, we also have
он не на пальцах сочетает Да у нас тоже
more we have more than 100
У нас больше у нас больше 100
nationalities in Ukraine
национальностей в Украине
someone tells you two can’t let
кто-то подсказывает вы двое не можете
me alone so they tell
давайте я один так те подсказывает Во
First of all the largest country in
первых во первых самая большая страна в
the world a large supply of natural oil  gas, the
мире большой запас нефти природного газа
first manned flight into outer space
первый полет человека в открытый космос
was not the first communications flight was not in
был не первый полет связи был не в
Russia
России
No, this is the Soviet Union one of the most
Нет это Советском Союзе одна из самых
what kind of countries are you wearing for the Olympics? at the
в чем вы на олимпиаду
Olympics, these FSB officers
у вас на Олимпиаде мочу эти фсбшники
changed the scandal; more, they
меняли скандал больше ваш
disqualified you from the Olympic Games. That
дисквалифицировали из олимпийской То
is, you couldn’t even do anything without doping.
есть вы без допинга без не смогли даже
What kind of
ничего Какая спорт
sport?  specifically Go
спортсменов стали специально Заходи
into that jar Yes, so that it is
зацикл в ту баночку Да чтобы она была
without doping it is such a disgrace
без допинга это такой позорище
sports disgrace to the whole world was
спортивное позорище на весь мир было
Let's
Давай
just mask it's real
просто маски это реально
with sports it's really not a word No
со спортом это реально не слова нет
I now,
к примеру Спортивная в том что я сейчас
as it were, programs to be slammed, it’s time for
как бы программ быть охлопнул пора
locks. I would, I would, I would, if
замках Я бы я бы я бы я бы я бы если бы
you were physically near me, you told me this.
ты был возле меня физически ты мне такое
And so you sit, you understand that
говорил А так ты сидишь ты понимаешь что
you won’t fly in now.  the
тебе сейчас не прилетит Ответ когда и ты
glory of Russia Let's
поэтому я бы в чем слава России Давай мы
click
нажимаем
on what the glory of Russia
в чем слава России
can Russia is a rich country
может Россия богатая страна
of course Where is your salary rich
конечно Где богатая у тебя зарплата
yu
вес имею
Look, here in Europe we
Смотри вот в Европе нам европейские
have European countries, for example, the rich compare
страны есть например богатые сравниваешь
another, come on
другой давай
How much do the United Arab Emirates earn with
Сколько зарабатывают Арабские Эмираты с
Russia and the United Arab Emirates with Russia Yes,
Россией и Арабские Эмираты с России да
you are like a nonentity settlement with the
вы типа [__] поселение с
Arab Emirates, you
арабскими эмиратами
can say a great country Glory to the
можно сказать великая страна Слава
Arab Emirate, you can say Glory to
арабским эмирата можно сказать Слава
Belgium, for example Glory to the United
Бельгии например Слава соединенным
States of America
штатам Америки
in  comparison Here you can imagine You,
в сравнении Вот представляешь Ты
for example, meet with Americans,
например встречаешься с американцами
say the words of Russia, we have the best
говоришь слова России у нас самые лучшие
discouraged, how many salaries are in Russia,
приуныл сколько вот зарплаты в России
Here is who you work
Вот ты кем работаешь
Well, I have weight with whom you work,
Ну вес имею с кем ты работаешь
here I am Well,
вот я
it’s good That’s who you work with, at
Ну это хорошо Вот И кем работаешь Я по
least I don’t hang a flag from behind and
крайней мере не вешу сзади флаг и
really, I’ll say rich Russia, I want to
реально я скажу Россия богатая хочу
understand how this wealth affects
понять Как это богатство отражается на
people a
людях
car you have of course
машина у тебя есть конечно
Cars no salary
Тачки нет зарплаты
no understands your insignificance in
нет понимает свою [__] в
comparison with European ones
сравнении там с европейскими
a lot of Russian culture at the highest
много российского Культура на высшем
level
уровне
What is the Russian culture of
Какая Российская культура
modern writers
современных писателей
well, we are no Russian writer a
ну нас никакого писателя российского
lot a lot For example  p
много очень много Например
wait, what kind of Russian writer do you
подожди какого ты писатель российского
know Come
знаешь Давай
on, you have a Morgenstern chipped in shorter yes
ушу вас моргенштерн обколотый короче да
Insta female This is your whole culture
Инста самка Вот это вся ваша культура
modern
каких-то вот знаешь современных деятелей
cultural figures of the Russian
культуры Российской
side Yes, not in the fact that now
стороны Да не в том то что сейчас
[ __ ] with your laughter, really before,
Бля вот своим смехом реально раньше
another country was the Russian Empire
другая страна была Российская империя
was Soviet, completely different countries,
был Советский совсем другие страны там
other peoples went there, for example, during
ходили другие народы например во время
the Russian Empire, we were with you in the
Российской империи мы были с вами в
same country, we built you helped
одной стране мы вам строили помогали
Ours were  these scientists And now that's what you're
Наши были эти ученые А сейчас вот что вы
great here we are from you what you have achieved
велика вот мы от вас что вы достигли
tell me for 30 years of your
скажи вот за 30 лет вашей Независимости
Russian Independence What is your culture the
российской Какая у вас культура самая
largest country
большая страна
China is large and for example Belgium is
Китай большой и например Бельгия
small Where people live better
небольшая Где люди живут лучше
Well of course in Russia with Russia
Ну конечно же в России
I will understand the level  your salaries,
я пойму уровень твоих зарплат
I just don’t
Я просто не тебе
adore these slovaroses that
обожаю вот этих словаросов которые
begin the words of Russia and here on that  which
начинают слова России и тут по таких
begins to unwind Tell me
начинает разматывать Расскажи мне
tell me what is the glory of your Russia
расскажи в чем Слава твоей России
Tell me come on let him let the bull go there damn it
Расскажи мне давай давай он там быку
subscribed to the channel
подписался на канал
simply for the elephant I have moments like
простотыщно на слона я вот такие моменты
this just such
бывают на это просто такие
intellectually emotive yes yes
интеллектуально эмотив
no quiz now I won’t come today
не викторины ща не буду сегодня
Cool damn I  just God cool
Классно блин я просто Боже круто
I think for a long time In short, a
Я думаю давно
big country Well, there is also a
Все короче большая страна Ну еще есть
divine one, there is some kind of
божественная есть маленькая какой-то там
Liechtenstein further than Switzerland,
Лихтенштейн дальше Швейцарии
people there live somehow cooler than in
люди там живут как-то покруче чем в
Russia, yes, that is, a
России да то есть
cool country from the vastness of the territory and
крутой страны от огромности территории а
the quality of life of citizens Russia
качестве жизни граждан Россия
developed countries need to develop  so that
развитые страны надо развиться так чтобы
people live better, the standard of living has increased, the
люди жили лучше уровень жизни повысился
death rate has decreased, the level of diseases has decreased there, the
уменьшилась смертность уменьшилась там
world
уровень заболеваний мир
is moving towards developing so these
идет к тому чтобы развиваться так эти
degradations are shorter, damn it, it’s just, damn, I’m
деграды короче блин просто ну блин я
crazy at least throwing a stream with us 6
побалдел хоть накидать стрима у нас 6
interesting to this
интересненько до такого